Okay, we split up and start working a bit on the house dreams, then.
That is why there is so much paper here.
- I think we should go to the kitchen.
- We go to the kitchen and you stay here.
Schas, schasome!
Fort, fast!
Go, go!
Away!
Schas, schasome, schasome!
- Bye!
- Laura takes nothing.
We have had some different ideas.
At first, Harry thought we would make a horror house.
“Poppy Pli Time”
- And then you were at a sushi restaurant.
- mm.
Since then we have been thinking a lot about which form-
-And concluded that the simplest thing is to just print finished shapes from the net.
So we have done that, and then we will invest more in the decoration itself.
And what kind of house will it be?
Do we know that?
Alma, what should we do?
Oh no!
You may do a new part.
No!
This must be possible to cook.
Everything can be cooked, especially in Portugal.
We have seen that.
Everything can be cooked with glaze.
The houses are oblique and wind, and they can still cook.
- Laura broke our freshly baked chimney.
- Laura, your little bus!
It can probably get together anyway, I think.
I hope.
Now we have all our pieces.
God, what I look like in my hair.
It's so hot when standing by the oven, or what do you say?
- Yes.
- You also look a little ... weather bite.
We started to try to put together our pieces with cold stuff like this "baking glue".
Was it a good idea?
- No.
- No, a very poor idea.
So now we have had it in a water bath.